Joey visited me?
I saw her downstairs, leaving.
- Zoey, was Joey here earlier?
- Yes.
And you barred her
from going in?
I am just protecting you
from her.
Leave. I don't want
to hurt you anymore.
Why don't we explore
private care for her?
Will mommy be away from us?
I want to go.
Jin Ho, we need your help.
Can we meet again?
Where are you going?
My friends rescheduled.
I'm just meeting them now.
We'll follow someone.
Joey, stop this.
What if they do something worse
to you?
Andrew, I don't want
that to happen
because I love you.
I love you, Andrew.
Joey...
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOBBING]
You know, a lot of people have
asked me how I feel for you.
But I didn't answer them
because I should admit it
to you first, right?
You should be the first to know.
Because this is the first time
I've ever felt this way.
I was even one
of your bashers, remember?
I didn't even like you.
But as we spent time together,
I became impressed with you.
You're amazing in everything
you do.
Your conviction is strong,
and you always help me,
you help my family.
I tried to stop myself
from liking you, but...
[STAMMERS]
I don't know.
Joey...
When I saw you hurt...
That's when I realized
you're so important to me.
- That I love you, Andrew.
- Joey, Joey...
I love you, Andrew.
Joey, this is wrong.
You're still young.
Joey, you don't know
what you're saying.
Age has nothing to do with it.
I know what I feel.
Joey, you only think that
because we're always together.
But those feelings...
Joey, they will change.
You're still young.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
You know,
I'd rather you reject me.
But to invalidate what I feel...
It makes me feel so small,
Andrew.
But it's okay.
At least now I know
how you feel.
If I ever did something,
showing you false hope,
I'm sorry.
I was careless.
If I made you expect.
I'm sorry, Joey.
If you're angry with me,
I'll accept it.
But please, Joey, listen to me.
Stop going after Jin Ho, please.
[TENSE PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
You're crazy!
Peter!
I'm a man, Andrew!
I saw everything you did
to Joey!
And what?
I know it's not just
because you're kind!
You made her hope!
You made her believe!
Then you say sorry
that you were careless?
Peter!
Joey!
What's happening?
Joey...
Why are you crying?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm sorry, Joey.
Maybe it's better...
if I stay away from you.
Yes, you should leave!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ENGINE STARTS]
Let's go inside.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Do you have feelings for her?
See?
You can't even admit it
to yourself, Andrew.
Because you know
you're not right for each other.
You're too different.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
What if they come back?
Andrew, I don't want that
to happen.
I won't allow that
to happen to you because...
- Enough.
- you're important to me.
- Joey, enough.
- I love you.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'm sorry, Joey.
I'm really, really sorry.
I'm sorry, I fought with Andrew
because he doesn't believe
in our plan with Jin Ho.
We got into a heated argument.
That's all?
It's seems like Andrew
doesn't trust our plan...
Joey just held us back
from getting in a fight.
So, I'm really sorry.
[HEAVY MUSIC PLAYING]
Child...
We won't force you to explain.
But if you want to say
something, remember...
your father and I are here.
Let's postpone our plan
about Jin Ho for another day.
No, Dad, please.
It would be a waste.
This is our chance.
It might be harder to catch
Jin Ho next time.
Can you really do it?
Everything is ready.
And we're all together.
So, you shouldn't worry,
Mom, Dad.
Fine, but...
Be careful, okay?
Let's finish this.
[HEAVY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Peter really is crazy.
He knows that you're all
beaten up,
yet he made things worse.
Can't you dodge, Boss?
You're so good at fighting.
You could easily handle Peter.
No need.
I deserve to be punched.
[LIGHT AMBIENT MUSIC PLAYING]
Because of what I did to Joey.
Why? What did you do?
I rejected her.
What?
[SCOFFS]
Joey? We're talking about Joey?
So?
Joey confessed her feelings
to you...
and you rejected her? Because?
It's obvious you have feelings
for Joey.
That's true, Boss.
We know.
You think you can hide it,
but it's obvious,
we can see that Joey
is special to you.
That's exactly it.
I don't want her to get hurt.
I rejected her
because I don't want to be
the reason
she'll put herself at risk
looking for Jin Ho.
I don't want her feelings
to be the reason she gets hurt.
Is that really all?
[DAUNTING MUSIC PLAYING]
Madam, we've been here
for an hour.
We'll wait until he leaves.
We'll wait as long as it takes.
[DAUNTING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Are we really going to do this
after everything Andrew said?
Let's just ignore him.
You heard all that?
Yes, sorry. I didn't mean to.
No, don't say sorry.
You're my best friend.
I don't hide anything from you.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Peter...
Why?
Peter, I just have one request.
Can you support me?
Do you really need to ask that?
Peter, I'm not doing this
just for Andrew.
I'm doing this for dad,
for my family.
I just want the syndicate
to get caught
so all this would end and our
lives can go back to normal.
Can you help me do that?
So, you can move on?
Of course, I'm in.
Let's go find Jin Ho.
Let's go.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Jin Ho...
Joey!
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
I thought you aren't coming.
What happened to Andrew?
How is he?
Why did you have Andrew
beaten up?
Or, you tried to have him killed
but you failed?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Don't pretend you don't know.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
So, what's next?
Will you have me
and Peter killed too
because we know the truth?
That you're part of
the syndicate? Is that it?
What?
Madam, are they fighting?
That woman looks familiar to me.
This could be her.
That means Jin Ho knows her.
The Korean is betraying you.
I don't know what you're talking
about.
I didn't do anything to Andrew.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
You were the only one who knew
we were going to that place
that night, right?
[SIGHS]
No, listen.
If I wanted to hurt him,
or any of you,
you wouldn't survive.
I came here because
I was worried about Andrew,
and I still want to help you.
But you're accusing me
of so many things!
[SIGHS]
Joey, maybe we should listen
to Jin Ho first.
We've been through things
together.
What I want is for him to tell
the truth.
Just tell us.
Where is the syndicate hiding
and who is Berdugo?
Okay, so you want to know
the truth?
Fine, I'll tell you.
Give me the gun.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
The truth is...
I don't owe any of you
any explanation.
I'm leaving.
Do not follow me.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Why, Madam?
Do you want me to take the shot?
Not yet.
We have to leave.
We have to get ahead of Jin Ho
before he reaches the warehouse.
And for that girl,
I'll deal with her
some other day.
I want to enjoy torturing her
first before killing her.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SLURPING]
So, you let Zoey poison
your mind?
You listened to her gaslighting,
is that it?
[PLEASANT AMBIENT MUSIC PLAYING]
That wasn't gaslighting.
She has a point.
I mean, it's not like...
I hadn't thought of it
before she told me.
Joey and I are just different.
She's...
She's too young for me.
Yes, she's younger than you,
but she's not naive, Andrew.
I think with everything she's
been through with her family,
she's already aware
of how the world works.
What's good about Joey is that
even when she sees the bad,
she doesn't lose hope.
That's what you need, Boss.
Your cynicism is balanced
by Joey's positivity.
Actually, yes.
Honestly, I actually think you
became a better man,
a better journalist even,
since you met Joey.
She's a good influence on you...
Despite the age gap
you keep making an issue.
There's really no issue, Boss.
But how?
The problem is Joey is still
hurt because of what Andrew did.
Would you forgive him
right away?
What? What did you say?
Nothing, Boss.
[ELAI CHUCKLES]
[CURIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Joey.
- Dad.
- How are you?
We were unable to make him
confess.
But still, mission accomplished.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Jin Ho isn't our only target.
He's just a small fish.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
He'll lead us to the depths
of the sea
where the sharks are.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CLACKS]
We placed a tracker
on Jin Ho's vehicle.
Last movement recorded
is at 2:17 AM.
Since then, he hasn't moved
from this area,
here at Bolivar Mushroom
Chips Manufacturing.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Is there prior intel
on this facility?
It's written here
in Ramon's notebook.
There's a mushroom chip
manufacturing in this area.
Maybe they changed the address
on the label,
that's why we got confused.
Some of our people also
did surveillance, Sir.
There are movements,
looks like deliveries.
And armed men are guarding
the compound.
Prepare coordination
with the RTC duty judge.
We'll expedite a search warrant.
And good thing I already spoke
with the DDE.
They'll be joining
the operation.
[KNOCK ON THE DOOR]
Sir.
[DAUNTING MUSIC PLAYING]
So, the rumors were true.
Major Miguel Delgado is alive.
And you've already reunited
with your daughter.
You know that Joey
is my daughter?
Yes, Sir.
She was with us in Valmora, Dad.
Andrew's friend.
Friend?
You know that we were
more than that.
[CLEARS THROAT]
All right, mission first.
Clarissa, can we have the room?
Sir, wait! What about Jin Ho?
What if you run into him?
What will happen to him?
If he fires at us,
we'll fire back.
We cannot guarantee
he'll be taken alive.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Elai, can we just air
a replay for now?
I really need to talk to Joey.
What you did to Joey
was very harsh.
I had to do it to protect her.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
But I know that I could've
handled it better.
I was wrong to hurt her,
especially when she had
the courage
to tell me what she feels.
How about you?
When will you have the courage
to tell her what you feel?
That wasn't part of the Bisaya
lessons you taught me.
[CHUCKLES]
Well, that's your problem.
- [PHONE RINGING]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Jin Ho, answer it
if you don't want to die.
Peter, what are you doing?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Who are you talking to?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
No one.
Let me see.
I said no one.
No...
[PHONE RINGING]
Don't call again.
I'm blocking you.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Peter, why are you calling
Jin Ho?
I just want to tell Jin
to leave the syndicate.
What?
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Do you really want to ruin
dad's operation?
Joey,
I just want Jin Ho
to save himself.
There's still hope
for our friend!
Joey, I know Jin Ho.
I've been with him
more than you and Andrew.
That's why I know
he was genuine with us.
He felt bad when he found out
we suspected him
with what happened to Andrew.
Fine, here's what I'll do.
I'll ask dad that,
as much as possible,
they won't hurt Jin Ho,
that they'll force him
to surrender.
Thank you.
I'll just find the right time
to talk to dad.
Joey, my phone...
I'll keep it for now.
You might warn Jin Ho again.
Peter, dad's operation
cannot fail.
We worked hard for this.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's a go, everyone.
You all know our objective.
Let's all be careful. Let's go!
Yes, Sir.
[GUN COCKS]
Miguel, wait.
Why? I thought you weren't
joining the operation?
Love, this is the last one.
I don't know.
I'm nervous, Miguel.
We have the element of surprise.
They don't know we're coming.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
This is the chance to bring down
the syndicate.
They destroyed our family,
so I need to be there.
Miguel...
That's why I admire you
so much, Dad.
Just be careful, okay?
Thank you.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
But, Dad...
Can you promise that
if you catch Jin Ho,
you won't hurt him?
Just arrest him.
I can't promise that,
my child...
But I'll try.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
- We have a search warrant.
- Search all you want.
- Secure this place!
- Did you see Peter?
- No, I didn't notice him.
- His phone is also gone.
Joey, don't be mad, okay?
But I'm here at the warehouse
to warn Jin Ho.
Peter, come on!
- Clear! Move!
- Where are they?
Stop! Hands in the air!
Drop your guns!
None of you will leave
this place alive!
I'm not leaving while my father
is inside fighting!
At long last, we meet, woman.
Do the honors, Jin Ho.
This is your last chance
to prove your loyalty.